Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographic material and paper records, Series 1
  - Contact sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Contact Sheets, September 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, October 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, November 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, December 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, January - April 1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, May - August 1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January - March 1969; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April - August 1969; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1969; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, January - March 1970; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, April - August 1970; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1970; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January - April 1971; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May - August 1971; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1971 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1971 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 41B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, January - April 1972; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, November 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, December 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, January 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, May 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, June 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, July 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, February 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, March 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, April 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, June 2002 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, June 2002 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, October 2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1961-1963 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1961-1963 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1965-1966 [1 of 4]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1965-1966 [2 of 4]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1965-1966 [3 of 4]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1965-1966 [4 of 4]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, February - April 1967; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August - December 1967; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March - April 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1977 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1977 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1977 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1977 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44C, Folder 6)
    - Aerials, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 1)
    - Aerials, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 2)
    - Aerials, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 3)
    - Aerials, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 4)
    - Aerials, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 5)
    - Aerials, 1983 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45A, Folder 6)
    - Aerials, 1983 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 1)
    - Aerials, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 2)
    - Aerials, November 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 3)
    - Aerials, March 1985 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 4)
    - Aerials, March 1985 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 5)
    - Historical 4x5's, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, May - August 1972; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, September - December 1972; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1973 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1973 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February - March 1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, April - May 1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, June -September 1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, October - December 1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January - February 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March - April 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, July - August 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, October - November 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 7)
    - Aerials, April 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47A, Folder 1)
    - Aerials, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47A, Folder 2)
    - Aerials, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47A, Folder 3)
    - Aerials, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47A, Folder 4)
    - Aerials, 1990 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47A, Folder 5)
    - Aerials, 1990 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 1)
    - Aerials, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 2)
    - Aerials, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 3)
    - Aerials, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 4)
    - Aerials, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48C, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 48C, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, February 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, March 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, April 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, May 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, June 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49C, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, July 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49C, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, August 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 49C, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1995; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1996; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 51B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 52B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42C, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 42C, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1997; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 56B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 57B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1989; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, July - August 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 59B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 85B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 39B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 39B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 39B, Folder 3)
    - File 1 - Contact Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 39B, Folder 4)
  - Color slides, Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Construction B-1, May 1974 - May 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Construction B-2, November 1970 - May 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Construction B-3 1, June 1972 - April 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Construction B-3 2, March 1974 - May 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Construction B-4, July 1971 - October 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Construction B-5, July 1971 - June 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Construction B-6 1, November 1971 - July 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Construction B-6 2, May 1976 - November 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Construction B-9, April 1981 - February 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Construction A-13 1, 1976 - 1980; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Construction A-13 2, 1982 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Construction A-14, 1979 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Construction A-15 Twinbrook, 1979 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Construction A-15 Rockville, 1979 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Construction A-16, 1982 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Construction A-17, 1979 - 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Construction B-1 1, 1966 - 1971; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Construction B-1 2, 1971 - 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Construction B-1 3, 1972 - 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Architecture - G File, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Badge, Bicycles, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Board 1, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Board 2, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Board 3, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Board 4, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Architecture: G - H, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Architecture: J - L, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Architecture: M, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Architecture: M - N, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Architecture: N, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Architecture: N - P, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Architecture: P, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Architecture: P - R, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Architecture: R - S, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Architecture: S, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Architecture: S - T, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Architecture: T - U, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Architecture: V - W, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Architecture: W - Z, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Art, Awards, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Bus: Garage Landover, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - APLHA Set, March 1988 - September 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 1)
    - Alvin McMeal, March 1983 - May 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 2)
    - Anacostia - D. Hale, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 3)
    - Benning Road, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 4)
    - BETA 8/29 Review, March 1987 - September 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 5)
    - BETA - 2, April 1992 - March 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 6)
    - Capitol Heights D. Hale, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 7)
    - Deanwood and Capitol Heights, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 8)
    - Dupont, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 9)
    - E Route Jerry Jani Coun, March 1987 - March 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 10)
    - File 3, June 1982 - April 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 11)
    - Ft. Totten, March 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 12)
    - Ft. Totten, Brookline, RI Ave, Ward 5 Sites - R. Daggett, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 13)
    - Ft. Totten, Rockville, Takoma, Western Scales, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 14)
    - Gallery Place Phil Scales, December 1993 - March 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 15)
    - Greenbelt, January 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 16)
    - H Street Phil Scales, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 17)
    - Huntington JMD, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 18)
    - MCI Center H Street Lot Al McMeal, 1998 January - 1999 May; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 19)
    - Minnesota Ave., 1993 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 20)
    - Navy Yard D. Hale, 1993 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 21)
    - New JDS, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 22)
    - Old Gallery Phil Scales, 1994 March - 2000 May; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 23)
    - R.I. Ave. and S.E. Bus, 1993 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 24)
    - Shaw D. Hale, 1993 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 25)
    - Silver Spring, Pentagon City, 1991 April - 1998 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 26)
    - Site plans, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 27)
    - Slides for new proposals, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 28)
    - Slide presentation Phil Scales, 1989 December - 1999 May; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 29)
    - U Street, 1993 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 30)
    - U Street metrorail station area Al McMeal, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 31)
    - Upcoming projects, 1999 May; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Sites, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Doug Hale, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Phil Scales [duplicates], Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 35)
    - Miscellanous [1/3], 1983 October - 1999 May; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous [2/3], 1988 June - 2001 December; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous [3/3], Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 38)
    - From Wayne Thompson, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 39)
    - Negatives, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 39A, Folder 40)
    - Construction C-4, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Construction C-5, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Construction C-6, C-6b, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Construction C-6e, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Construction C-7, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Construction C-8, C-8a, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Construction C-8b, c, d, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Construction C-9, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Construction B-10 1, October 1984 - November 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 1)